<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-06-29T14:58:50-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Gary’s Progress</title><entry><title type="html">Daythree</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/DayThree/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Daythree" /><published>2018-06-29T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-06-29T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/DayThree</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/DayThree/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;afternoon-update&quot;&gt;Afternoon update&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The intubation tube has finally been removed and Gary is now breathing on his own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is currently using an oxygen mask that is treating the swelling and irritation in his throat with a cool air mist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’s resting not so comfortably and is a little agitated by not being allowed to talk. The doctors have asked him to refrain from speaking for a few hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gary was able to get a couple of words in though after the doctor denied his request for some ice. The doctor told Gary “nope, can’t have that right now sorry” and he responded with “oh fuck.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gary is back.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Afternoon update</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Daytwo</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/DayTwo/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Daytwo" /><published>2018-06-28T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-06-28T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/DayTwo</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/DayTwo/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;evening-update&quot;&gt;Evening update&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The heart pump (Impella) has successfully been removed and Gary is doing very well. The doctors believe he is making great progress and doing well without the heart pump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gary is able to answer direct questions by blinking and nodding. Vitals are improving and we are hopeful that he will have the intubation tube removed within the next few days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The doctors have decided to sedate him for the night so he can relax post-procedure. For the rest of this evening and throughout the day tomorrow, they’re primary goal is to increase the dialysis fluid removal rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;morning-update&quot;&gt;Morning update&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night, a procedure was done to remove some more fluid from Gary’s lungs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is slightly more coherent and has shown, by nodding his head and blinking his eyes, that he recognizes Kimberly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The heart pump is still scheduled to be removed later today, so we will provide another update after that procedure.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Evening update</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dayone</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/DayOne/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dayone" /><published>2018-06-27T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-06-27T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/DayOne</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/DayOne/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;todays-update&quot;&gt;Today’s update&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although Gary is ready to have the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abiomed.com/impella&quot;&gt;Impella&lt;/a&gt; heart pump removed, the removal has been postponed until some time tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As most of you know, Gary suffered a “widowmaker” heart attack on Thursday and is currently on life support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, he was with rescue when he coded and was able to receive CPR immediately. He was placed on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chop.edu/treatments/extracorporeal-membrane-oxygenation-ecmo&quot;&gt;ECMO&lt;/a&gt; and we believe it has saved his life. Gary came off ECMO on Monday, but he is still intubated and on an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abiomed.com/impella&quot;&gt;Impella&lt;/a&gt; heart pump and is on dialysis. He has been able to respond to commands, but is mostly incoherent and agitated over the intubation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite some other complications, there have been great daily improvements. He has a long battle ahead of him, but we have faith and hope that he will recover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has become overwhelming updating everyone individually so we have put together this web page to keep all of our concerned friends and family members up to date on Gary’s progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We appreciate all of your support and we will try to post updates about Gary’s progress once or twice per day to keep you all informed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, thank you all for your support during this difficult time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kimberly, Melissa, Brieonna, Michael and Brandon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- &lt;br/&gt;

--- --&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Today’s update</summary></entry></feed>